[{"answer": "ASEY: Well, just how broken these families were and how devastated they were by this tragedy.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "When you watch that interview that I did with the Soto family, what was it about that that particularly struck you?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, they may, and they probably will at some point.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "You are making an enemy of the NRA now with what you're doing and they will come after you, won't they?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "I'm 20 years old.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "But what do you say to those politicians, the senators up there, who are more interested in saving their seat politically than in doing something to prevent another Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Do you think it has any place in civilian life?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "It was amazing.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "What was that experience like for you?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Personally, I feel like we haven't seen the crime scene photos.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Do you think there's any merit to that argument?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "He used, the shooter, 30-bullet magazines.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Do you really need to see the pictures also?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "The youngest boy, Noah, was shot 11 times.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "What do you say?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Definitely.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Do you think that some of the children may have survived if he hadn't had such a high-capacity magazine in his weapons?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "I think he's doing an amazing job.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Are you happy with what he is trying to achieve here?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, it's very much a guessing game, just like we were guessing yesterday, along with the U.S. government and the South Korean government.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "What is likely to happen, do you think, over the next 24 or 36 hours?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "It's a great question.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Nick Kristof (ph)?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, what do you mean by -- if there is --", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Would it be America or China?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "The U.S. will be the central force there.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "-- for example, took any action directly against South Korea, for example, who would you expect to lead any kind of retaliatory action?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, our organization, the Independent Firearm Owners, supports universal background checks for people who don't know each other.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "I mean, do you still believe there's no need for universal background checks?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Well, there is a lot of truth to what they say.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "When you see the NRA statement which said expanding background checks at gun shows will not prevent the next shooting or not solve violent crime or not keep our kids safe in schools, do you disagree with that?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well, 20 percent of all gun sales are done without background checks.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "When you see that happening, what is your reaction?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Well, first thanks for having me.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "An expansion of background checks?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Piers, there's a number of people in Washington who are trying to do various things in regard to preventing gun violence, and background checks, stopping straw purchases, stopping gun trafficking, those are the first steps.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "And how can it restart to reflect the wider public opinion in America?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Uh-huh.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "A Glock .9 millimeter?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "I think it's a reminder that most crime happens within families.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What is the idea you came up with?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I think that we should not restrict women's rights to have access to firearms.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Gayle Trotter, what is your view of the call for universal background checks?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Because 90 percent of violent crimes happen without the use of firearms.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Why just women?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Limitations if they're either mentally disturbed or criminally minded?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "So we are already --", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "So what?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "The point that I made is most women when they're violently attacked, their attacker does not have a gun.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "What is the point?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "Well, I testified before the Senate Judiciary Committee in January and I had over 20 examples of women defending themselves and their loved ones with firearms.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Why wouldn't you want to flag those people up and stop them from buying guns?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Because the Second Amendment --", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Why do you not want to flag out people that may want to harm women?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Can I ask you a question about those restrictions?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "No, he should not.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "What about if a man has a domestic violence restraining order against him, should he be allowed to buy a gun?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Well, that's the guy we were talking about earlier.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Well, how do you know?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "The audience is sharing my bemusement as to why you want -- you can't answer a simple question.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Would you like to hear about the study?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "-- allow someone to be armed in the place that she was.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "Why wouldn't you want a background check to protect her?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "Educate women to know that guns make women safer.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "But why wouldn't you want to stop them from getting a gun?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "So it would be more helpful to women if you highlighted the cases of women --", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Why wouldn't you stop him getting a gun?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "-- defending themselves and their families and their vulnerable family members from violent attackers with guns.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "We'd all help because (INAUDIBLE) guns?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130410pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Jeffrey, am I going mad?", "qSentId": 664}]